

Steve Li

Software Developer

SKILLS

C/C++

Javascript

Firebase

Python

Git

Java

HTML

Jquery

CSS

Qt

MySQL

CONTACT INFO

+1 978-735-3386 lithafnium2000@gmail.com https://lithafnium.github.io

ABOUT

I am an aspiring coder with over 7 years of programming experience with a penchant for design and function. I am passionate about enhancing user experience as well as making a difference in the world. Through code, I am able to express my intellectual side as I continue to positively impact the lives of others.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CO-FOUNDER & SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

Vitaedev | Mar 2016 - Mar 2018

- Student-run organization, creates websites for community organizations in need for one free of charge
- Worked as a full-stack web developer: HTML5, CSS3, PHP, MySQL, and Git
- https://vitaedev.github.io/

TEACHER'S ASSISTANT

KtByte | Sep 2016 - PRESENT

- Teacher's Assistant at KtByte Computer Academy, a computer academy based in Lexington, MA
- Taught Java and Processing, managing students and aiding in questions, grading homeworks, etc.
- https://www.ktbyte.com/

ANDROID DEVELOPER

Mass General Hospital | Jan 2015 - Jun 2015

- Worked as an Android Developer and created MySQL data-tables in collaboration with Dr. Alvin Yu for the CADI Project, a web application checklist for surgeons and other doctors

SOFTWARE RESEARCH INTERN

Brigham and Women's Hospital | Jul 2018 - Aug 2017

- Worked with Professor Junichi Tokuda to create a voice-enabled extension for the 3D-imaging tool, "3D Slicer," in order to make operating procedures more efficient and streamlined

EDUCATION

CONCORD CARLISLE REGIONAL HIGH SCHOOL

Aug 2015 - Jun 2019

- GPA (unweighted): 3.95
- GPA (weighted): 4.45